翻译校对       Mam
日  听      マキ
日听校对       Syura
翻译        小袖
时间轴       黑猫与牛奶
压制      娜夏
OP&ED       葉隠
Syura
诸神字幕组
Hikaru, your cell phone is ringing...
光　携帯鳴ってる
光
Hikaru...
Kaoru, you answer it...
馨　出てよ
Oh, no... that ringtone is his highness's.
イヤだよ　その着信メロディ　殿じゃん
Why should we have to be
awakened three mornings
何で夏休み三日目の朝からこんな着メロで起きなきゃなんないんだよ
into summer vacation by his ringtone?
He wakes up too early.
あの人　早起きしすぎ
Hello?
My daughter! My daughter is gone!
I can't get through to her!
うちの娘が　うちの娘がいない
連絡が付けない
誘拐されたに違いない　警察に連絡を
She must have been kidnapped!
Contact the police!
We have to request an emergency
deployment of the SDF, just in case!
場合によっては　自衛隊に緊急出動を要請せねば
Hold on, sir, calm down. What, now?
ちょっと　殿　落ち着いてよ　何
はっ？　ハルヒが行方不明？
Huh!? Haruhi has gone missing!?
Eh? Haru-chan has gone missing?
へっ？　ハルちゃんが行方不明？
Bankrupt, and fled by night?
破産で夜逃げ
That's right! I've called her
every day, again and again,
そうなんだ
夏休み初日から　毎日何度電話してもいないし
since the first day of summer vacation,
and I can't get through
to her papa's work, either!
パパさんの職場にも連絡がつかない
"Host Club conference call"
I'm sure they were unable to pay their rent,
and were forced into servitude!
きっと家賃が払えず　無理矢理奉公に出されたのだ
Otherwise, why else would
they flee into the night!?
さもなくば夜逃げか
Waah! Haru-chan!
ハルちゃん…
Sir, you're too loud.
You could just call her cell phone.
"Idi-" "-ots"
でか過ぎ
携帯に連絡すりゃいいから
携帯？　ハルヒがそんなもん持つか
Cell phone?
You think Haruhi would
have something like that!?
I know... There is a secret society
among the commoners,
俺は知ってるぞ
庶民の間には夜逃げ屋という秘密結社があって…
called the "fly-by-nighters."
Forgive me for interrupting
your dramatic delusion,
ドラマチックな妄想中申し訳ないが
ハルヒなら軽井沢だぞ
but Haruhi is in Karuizawa.
"Karuizawa?"
ハルヒが
Not only did Haruhi go bankrupt,
flee by night, and get kidnapped,
破産で
夜逃げで
誘拐されたうえに
but she's in Karuizawa?
軽井沢に？
落ち着け
Calm down.
ありがとうございました
Thank you very much.
"Pension Misuzu"
Welcome!
いらっしゃいませ
I've come to Karuizawa
to spend my summer vacation
夏休みを利用して
軽井沢のペンションにアルバイトにやってきました
working at a bed & breakfast.
So Haruhi is in Karuizawa.
ハルヒ　軽井沢だってさ
Yep.
- Good morning.
おはようございます
Good morning.
おはよう
- Your breakfast is ready.
朝食のご用意はできております
All right, we'll be right there.
分かった　すぐ行くよ
- Excuse us.
失礼いたします
It's just no fun not having
any of our playthings around, huh?
やっぱおもちゃいないと　始まらないなぁ
I was a little anxious about not
telling anyone in the Host Club
ホスト部のみんなに黙ってきたのが少し気がかりだけど
that I would be coming here,
さすがにこんなところまで邪魔しに来るほど暇じゃないだろうし
but I doubt that even
they have so little to do
that they'd come bother me
all the way out here.
The scenery is nice,
and the air is delightful.
景色が良くて　空気は美味しい
I should be able to get some
studying done up in these highlands.
こんな高原なら　勉強も捗りそう
This year, my summer vacation...
今年の夏休みは…
Haruhi!!
ハルヒ　無事か　お父さんが来たぞ
Are you all right!? Daddy is here!!
... could just be the worst vacation ever.
最悪の休みになりそうです
"Pension Misuzu"
My word!
What cute boys we have here!
Are you all friends of Haruhi?
可愛い坊やたちだこと
"Owner, Misuzu Sonoda, 42"
みんなハルヒちゃんのお知り合い？
"Real name: Isao Sonoda"
ふりふりのオカマさん
He's a flittering tranny.
You can call me Susuzu-chi!
美鈴っちで呼んでね
He was a friend of Ranka- san,
together at the same shop, way back.
蘭花さんとは昔　お店の仲間でいらっしゃったんだ
How do you know that?
なんでお前が知ってるんだ
Yeah, really.
本当に
I started this business here two years ago.
二年前からこっちでこの仕事始めたの
It was my dream, you know?
Running this adorable pension!
夢だったのよねぇ
こういう可愛いペンション
But why is Haru-chan working here?
でも　なんでハルちゃん働いてんの
Ranka- san is away on business,
and while he's away,
蘭花さんが社員旅行だから
その留守中　ハルヒのことが心配なので
he's worried about Haruhi,
so he had him take her in.
預かっていただくことになったんだ
Like I said, how do you know this?
だから　なんでお前が知ってるんだ
本当に
Yeah, really.
預かるだなん～て　うちはまだ従業員雇うほどの余裕ないから
Take her in, he says! I still
can't afford to hire any employees,
so having Haruhi come here
has been a tremendous help!
ハルヒちゃんが来てくれて大助かるよ
本当働き者で　バイト代安いのは申し訳ないくらい
She's really such a hard worker,
I feel sorry that her wages are so low.
このハルヒちゃんのエプロン　可愛いでしょう
Oh, Haruhi-chan, you're so cute
in that apron! I made it by hand!
私のお手製
And you did a good job, at that, Misuzu-chi!
それについてはグッジョブ　美鈴っち
A job, huh?
バイトとはね
So that's why you turned down
our invitation to go to Bali, is it?
だらか僕らが誘ったバリー行きも断ったのか
And we asked her to go along
with us to Switzerland, huh?
僕らも一緒にスイス行こうって言ったのにね
Yeah.
I don't have a passport, after all.
パスポート持ってないですから
Which is why I suggested that we use
だから　うちの国内リゾート安く使えばと提案したんだが…
one of our domestic resorts,
at a discount.
How come you guys are inviting
Haruhi out by yourselves like this?
お前らは　なぜそうやって　個人的にハルヒを誘ってるんだ
自分さえよければいいのか
Are you just out for yourselves?
Have you no sense of solidarity?
連帯感は皆無か
I work so hard as your president,
day in and day out,
俺などは部長として
みんなで一緒に楽しめるプランを毎日毎日一生懸命…
to come up with plans so that all of us
can enjoy ourselves together...
You turned off your cell, didn't you?
携帯切ってたろう
You can't do that!
ダメじゃん
But it's such a pain.
だって　面倒くさいんだよ
"Cell?"
You've got a cell, did you say?
携帯　持ってるだと？
Yeah, but I should say,
it's one that we've lent to Haruhi.
ああ　言っとくけど　僕らがハルヒに貸してるんだからね
By the way, it's one
that's only for friends.
因みに　お友達専用だから
Sir, you're our "senpai," and all.
殿は先輩　だもんね
"Buddies"
お友達
That must be nice, huh?
いいなぁ　それ
"Daddy and Buddy"
Then, I'm also in the "friends"
category that includes daddies.
では　俺もお父さんというお友達カテゴリーで…
There is no such friends category.
そんなお友達カテゴリーはありません
Look, just leave, please, everyone.
いいから　もう　みんな帰ってください
We'll all see each other
come the new term anyhow,
どうせ新学期になれば　嫌でも毎日会うんだから
whether we want to or not.
We're all free to spend our
vacations on our own, right?
休みをどう過ごそうと個人の自由でしょう
School rule number 9:
Part-time work is prohibited.
校則第九条　アルバイトを禁ず
Er... um... is that right?
あの　そうでしたっけ
Did you hear? That girl has a job
without the school's permission!
ご存知？
あちら学校に無断でアルバイトされてるんですって
My, she has some nerve, huh?
まぁ　いい度胸ですこと
"Karuizawa Guidebook"
It's nice to come out to
Karuizawa once in a while,
たまには軽井沢で避暑も渋くていいよね
to get out of the heat, huh?
海外も飽きましたしね
I have gotten tired of going overseas.
It is true, you are free to spend
your vacation on your own.
確かに　休みをどう過ごそうと個人の自由
In which case, you would
have no grounds to stop us.
ならば　お前に止める権利などないはず
Let's all stay here at this pension,
in the VIP guest rooms.
我々も　ビップ客として　このペンションに滞在させていただこう
N-no!!
イヤだ　イヤだ　イヤだ…
Good morning, my sleepy-headed Senpai.
お寝坊さんの先輩　おはようございます
Haruhi made you some breakfast.
ハルヒの作った朝食ですよ
Oh, good morning. Come on over here,
and let's eat together.
おはよう　こっちへおいで　一緒に食べよう
No, mm-mm, Senpai, you're a guest here,
and Haruhi is an employee.
いえ　ううん　先輩はお客さまで　ハルヒは従業員ですから…
When it's just the two of us,
we don't need to worry about that, do we?
二人きりの時は　そんなこと気にしなくていいじゃないか
You need only stay here, next to me.
お前はただ　俺のそばにいてくれればいいんだ
先輩…
Senpai...
"The Theatre of Tamaki's Mind
(in Karuizawa)"
Nice!
Um... Senpai?
あのう　先輩？
I'm sorry, I'd like to let
all of you stay here,
ごめんなさいね　全員泊めてあげたいけど
but unfortunately, I only
have one guest room available.
あいにく客室の空きは一部屋しかないの
Just one room, you say?
What else can be done?
一部屋…だけなのか
仕方ない
Very well, I, the president,
will represent everyone.
では代表して部長の俺が…
タマちゃんずるい
Tama-chan, no fair!
Are you just out for yourself?
Have you no sense of solidarity?
自分さえよければいいのか
連帯感は皆無か
You're the one who was
complaining so much about it before.
とか散々文句言ってたくせに
Am I being unfair?
Am I out for only myself?
俺って　ずるい子？
自分さえよければいい子？
Hey, sir, we just came up with
a fun game. Want to play with us?
ねね　殿
面白いゲーム思いついたんだけど　参加する？
We call it the " Guestroom refreshing
job contest in Karuizawa."
名づけて　「客室争奪戦さわやかアルバイトin軽井沢」
"Guest Relations Odd-Jobs Contest"
We'll work all day here at this pension,
今日一日人手が足りないというこのペンションでアルバイトする
where they say they are shorthanded.
そして　美鈴さんが一番好感度が高いと思った者がここの客になれる
And, whoever leaves the
best impression on Misuzu- san
"At Pension Misuzu"
gets to stay as the guest.
面白い　いいわいいわ　乗ったわ　その企画
Sounds fun! All right, all right,
I'm in on this plan!
Yes, if the one who I choose
as most refreshing stays here,
"Manager mode"
そう　私の選ぶ爽やか～な子が滞在するなら
then it will undoubtedly lead to
increased popularity for my pension!
このペンションの人気にも繋がること　間違いなしね
Our finest regards to you!
よろしくお願いします
びしびしと働いてもらうわよ
I'm going to work you to the bone!
Until I make my decision,
I will not treat you as guests!
決まるまで客扱いはしませんから
"Summer vacation..."
"...is now over."
Ha ha... sounds like fun...
楽しそうだなぁ
"And so"
You know, this is the first time in
my life that I've ever held a hammer.
しかし　金槌というものを生まれて初めて手にしましたよ
A job can be pretty harsh, huh?
仕事って厳しいよねぇ
You there! Complaining is forbidden!
Minus three points!
はい　そこ　愚痴は禁止　マイナス３点
It hurts... it hurts...
痛い　痛いです…
You look disgraceful.
That's minus another- hmm?
見苦しいから　さらにマイナス…
You can't persuade me
with cuteness, either!
可愛い子お強請りしてもダメ
Hi! Come on in!
はい　いらっしゃいませ
W-we have reservations to stay here.
しゅ…宿泊の予約をしたものですが…
Ah, yes, yes, we've been expecting you.
ああ　はいはい　お待ちしてました
Make yourselves at home, okay?
ゆっくりしててね
Allow us to show our
booked guests to their room.
予約のお客さん　お部屋にご案内で～す
They are quite forward,
but they are loveable characters,
態度はでかいけど　憎めないキャラなので
so plus five refreshment level points.
爽やか度プラス５点…
Oh, Takashi- kun, the legs
on that table are wobbly.
崇君　そこのテーブル　足が緩いのよ
Could you fix it for me, out in the yard?
庭で直してもらえるかしら
Understood.
了解
言動に無駄がないわ
Nothing wasted in word or deed!
Plus five refreshment level points.
爽やか度プラス５点
あのう　爽やか度って？
Um, what's a refreshment level?
ハルヒちゃん
Haruhi-chan, do you know
what guests are after
お客さんたちはこの軽井沢に何を求めて来てるか分かる
when they come here to Karuizawa?
えーと　涼しさ　とか？
Let's see... the cooler weather?
それだけじゃないわ
That's not the only reason.
It's what they can't experience
in the city- the refreshing air,
都会では味わえない爽やかな風　爽やかな景色
the refreshing scenery,
and the refreshing boys!
そして　爽やかな男の子たち
They all come here to Karuizawa
in search of refreshment.
みんなはこの軽井沢に爽やかさを求めて足を運んでくるの
This is a contest for them to see
who has the most refreshing appeal
これは彼らが軽井沢に来た女の子たちに
to the girls who have
come here to Karuizawa!
どれだけ爽やかさをアピールできるかという勝負なのよ
本当　楽しそうだな
That really sounds like fun...
Or should I say, this vividly calls
to mind a certain someone else.
ていうか　猛烈に誰かを思い出すんですけど
Then again, this is just like
how it is at the Host Club, at school.
でもこれじゃ　学校のホスト部と同じだよなぁ
Kyoya- senpai, you're not
taking part in the game, are you?
鏡夜先輩はゲームに参加しないんですね
No. Even if I did win,
あ　勝ったところで
it wouldn't do me any good
to stay by myself at this pension.
こんなペンションに一人で泊まっても仕方がないからな
I'll just watch here as much as I like,
and then leave for the cottage.
適当に見物でもして　後は別荘に引き上げるさ
Cottage? You mean,
your family's, Kyoya- senpai?
別荘？鏡夜先輩んちのですか
Yes, that's right.
そうだが　この辺りには　みんな持ってるよ
Everyone has one in the area.
泊まる所あるじゃん　なら　みんなそっち行けよ
Then they do have places to stay.
So go stay there, guys.
So then, about this refreshing contest...
それでこの爽やか勝負　ハルヒは誰が勝つと思う
Who do you think will win, Haruhi?
Shall we bet on it?
賭けようか
No thanks. I have no idea.
イヤです　全然分かりません
No, huh? It's easy to tell
from just a glance.
そうか　ぱっと見なら簡単だぞ
First off, Honey- senpai is visually
more "cute" than "refreshing,"
先ずハニー先輩はビジュアル的には爽やかというより可愛いだから
so he's out, right?
アウトだろ
環は黙っていれば爽やかだろうが
Tamaki may be refreshing,
when he keeps his mouth closed,
but he's too heated up
about winning the contest.
勝負に熱くなりすぎてる
ぶっちゃけ暑苦しい
He's flat-out sweltering.
普通に見れば　光馨だろうが
Ordinarily, you'd figure
it's Hikaru and Kaoru...
However, we have a dark horse.
しかし　大穴がいる
"Chopping firewood, for some reason"
Fantastic!
素敵
"and yet, super-refreshing!"
Refreshing!
爽やか
プラス２０点
Plus 20 points!
So then, it's Mori- senpai?
それじゃ　モリ先輩が？
However, if Honey- senpai drops out,
Mori- senpai will back out, too.
だが　ハニー先輩が脱落すればモリ先輩も辞退するだろう
He's only in this to tag along
with him to begin with, after all.
もともと付き合いで参加しているだけだからな
Which means...
となると
やっぱり　僕らで決まりだね
...that clinches it for us, all right.
Oh, yeah, I noticed earlier that
the available room is only a single,
あっ　そうだ　先気付いたんだけど
空いてる客室ってシングルだから
so even if you won,
both of you couldn't stay.
勝っても二人は無理だよ
Oh, that's okay. We'll bring
a bed over from our cottage.
ああ　大丈夫　うちの別荘からベッドを運ぶし
Even if we don't, we can squeeze
ourselves in and sleep together.
ダメでも無理矢理二人で寝るから
You two really are always
together, aren't you?
本当にいつも一緒なんだね
I suppose.
まぁね
We were together when we were born,
生まれた時から一緒だし
and we never had any other friends.
他に友達もいなかったし
Up until a few years ago,
やあ僕ら　数年前まで世の中はアボばっかと思ってたからさ
we thought the whole world was
made up of nothing but idiots.
You don't say.
But then...
We wouldn't mind including you, Haruhi.
ハルヒなら　混ぜてもいいよ
How about the three of us sleep together?
これからは三人で寝よっか
No, I'll pass.
いえ　遠慮しときます
The contest hasn't been decided yet.
まだ勝負が決まったわけじゃない
There are many ways to make
this game more interesting.
ゲームを面白くする方法はいくらでもあるが
この人こそ　腹黒さが突き抜けてて　一層爽やかだよな
This guy is always scheming something,
which makes him that
much more refreshing, huh?
Huh? Kyoya- senpai, are you
thinking of assisting his highness?
あれ　鏡夜先輩　殿に加勢する気？
Even so, we don't intend to lose.
それでも負ける気はしないけどね
Owner, I'm done fixing the fence.
オーナー　　柵の修繕完了
"Reporting in refreshingly"
"but repaired grotesquely"
The finished work is
completely unrefreshing.
仕上がりが全然爽やかじゃない
Minus three points.
マイナス３点
He's trying too frantically
to be refreshing,
爽やかであることに必死すぎて　仕事が完全に疎かに
so he's utterly negligent in his work.
Is he right in the head?
頭悪いのかな
He's never held a job before, you see.
もともとバイトなどしたことがないからなぁ
Ah, that's cold!
冷たいよ
Sorry, sorry. Look,
the watermelon is chilled.
ごめんごめん
ほら　スイカ冷やしてあるから　お客さんと一緒に食べよう
Let's eat it together with our guests.
- Wow, how refreshing!
爽やか
Oh, no... at this rate,
I'm going to lose to them...
いかん　このままではやつらに負ける
何としても勝ちたい
I want to win this, no matter what.
I want to win, and deepen
my friendship with Haruhi,
勝って　ハルヒと親睦を深め
そして　必ずや　ハルヒ公認のお友達カテゴリーに入らねば
and then...
I have to make sure I get into
Haruhi's official "friends" category!
Before going into how low
you set your goals,
目標が低いとか以前に
could you try not to be so melancholy?
物悲しくならないのか　お前は
Kyoya, can't you understand how I feel,
as a father for his daughter?
鏡夜　お前は娘を持ったこの父の気持ちが分からないのか
Let me offer you one bit of advice.
一つだけ知恵を貸してやろう
This is a trick that only you can pull off.
これはお前にしかできない技だ
Just don't mess up your music selection.
ただし　選曲をミスるなよ
Let's stop in here for some tea.
ここでお茶していきましょうよ
We've been done in.
やられたな
Huh?
あれ　馨一人？　光は？
Kaoru, are you by yourself? Where's Hikaru?
ゴミ袋取りに行ってるよ
He went to go get some garbage bags.
Oh.
You think you're going to win the contest?
勝負は勝てそう？
I'm not sure.
どうかな
That's Kyoya- senpai for you.
さすが鏡夜先輩
His highness didn't even realize
that there was a piano here.
殿はピアノの存在にすら気付いてなかったのに
Look out!
危ない
I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!
Are you all right!?
ごめんなさい　ごめんなさい
大丈夫ですか
It was close, but we're safe.
ぎりぎりセーフです　な？
- Right?
- Uh, yeah. Thanks.
うん　ありがとう
Kaoru!
馨
Kaoru, you've got a cut on your face!
馨　顔に傷が
Mm-hmm, I got a little cut.
うん　ちょっと切っただけ
Hikaru?
光？
Don't scare me like that.
驚かせんな
Mm-hmm, sorry. I'm all right.
ごめん　大丈夫だから
Bravo! Bravo!
ブラボー　ブラボーよ
What fantastic, refreshing brotherly love!
爽やか兄弟愛素敵
Misuzu-chi is touched!
100 points, perfect score!
美鈴っち感動　百点満点
勝者は　常陸院ブラザーズよ
The winners are the Hitachiin Brothers!
It can't be... seriously?
そんな…マジで
Congratulations.
おめでとう
どういたしまして
Don't mention it.
ちょ…ちょっと　まさか
H-hold on, you don't mean...
That was... planned?
今の　作戦？
Well now, who can say?
さぁね　どうでしょう
Really, I'm all right.
本当に大丈夫だから
Besides, we won without having to use
それに　爽やか兄弟喧嘩作戦やんなくて済んじゃったじゃん
our refreshing brother's quarrel plan, right?
Mm-hmm.
だ～か～ら　悪かったって言ってるじゃん　馨
I told you,
I said I was sorry, didn't I, Kaoru?
I don't remember kicking you out of the bed.
蹴落とした記憶ないんだから　しょうがないだろう
What am I supposed to do?
I slept on the cold floor,
and now my back hurts.
冷たい床で寝て　背中が痛い
Breakfast, please.
朝ご飯頂戴
I'll have toast with Brest butter
and garnet seal syrup.
トーストにプレスト社のバターとガーネット印のシロップね
Also, bacon and eggs,
and I'll take some Beasley cereal.
あと玉子とベーコンと　僕はビズリー社のシリアルにして
ドライフルーツ入れのやつ
The kind with the
dried fruit in it. After that...
"Arai Produce"
それからね…
ちょっと　そんなのここのメニューにないよ
Hold on.
We don't have that on the menu here.
Hey, you!
コラ！わがまま言うな　悪魔兄弟が
Don't be so fussy, you fiendish brothers!
Do you think you're some
sort of affluent aristocracy!?
お前らはどこぞの金持ちの貴族にでもなったつもりか
Well, actually, it's the truth.
いや　実際そうなんだけど
And I might point out, so are you.
つーか　あんたもだろ
"When in Rome, do as the Romans do,"
that's my general rule.
郷に入っては郷に従え　これ原則
When in Karuizawa, enjoy Karuizawa.
That's my ironclad rule.
軽井沢では軽井沢の時を楽しめ　これ鉄則
Cold pasteurized Jersey steaks,
低温殺菌のジャージ種に信州産のフレッシュジュース
with fresh juice from Shinano,
highland vegetables,
and the finest smoked salmon,
高原野菜と当地自慢の桜のチップでじっくり作った燻製は絶品だぞ
cooked slowly over cherrywood chips,
which are the pride of the local community.
Freshly baked Campagne breads,
with homemade jam,
焼き立てのカンパーニュには
素材本来の味を生かした手作りジャムをどうぞ
so you can taste the natural flavor
of the ingredients. Help yourself.
Why have you become...
なんでそんなにも
...such a huge fan of Nagano?
長野マニアなわけ？
He came here too early this morning,
and had nothing else to do,
朝早く来すぎて暇なもんだから
so Misuzu- san showed him everything.
美鈴さんが教え込んだんだよ
This goes like this, see?
これでこれでね
うんうん　なるほど
Mm-hmm, I see.
"Host Club Summer Training Camp"
While you were slumbering the day away,
お前らが惰眠を貪ってる間に　合宿のしおりも作成したんだぞ
I even made up a guide
for our training camp.
Such is the thoughtfulness
of your president.
部長の心配りだ
You really don't have
anything to do, do you?
本当に暇なんですね
Haruhi, while you are in training here,
"No senpai - friend - Top Five"
ハルヒは合宿中　俺を先輩扱いしないこと
you are not to treat me as your Senpai.
That is the first of the rules in here.
お約束第一条だよ
Uh-huh...
何これ　お約束第五条　朝６時起床とか書いてあんじゃん
What is this? It's written in here
that rule number 5 is to get up at 6 a.m.
Are Kyoya- senpai and
Honey- senpai observing these?
鏡夜先輩とハニー先輩は守ってんの　これ
"Eye of the Devil"
"Eyes of the Beast"
Oh, sorry, sorry, sir.
ごめんごめん　殿
We made you remember
something terribly scary, huh?
すごく怖い思いしたんだね
おかあさん
'lo! Arai Produce!
ちはーす　荒井青果です
Okay, thanks so much. Huh? A working boy?
はい　ご苦労様
あら　バイトの子？高校生？
Are you in high school?
Yes, I'm just helping out at
my uncle's shop over summer vacation.
はい　夏休みの間だけ　おじの店の手伝いに
もう～　爽やか
My, how refreshing!
Haruhi-chan, would you put these
in the refrigerator for me?
ハルヒちゃん　これ　冷蔵庫にお願いね
Yes.
Haruhi? Fujioka Haruhi?
ハルヒって　藤岡ハルヒ？
Arai- kun!
荒井君
Why should Hikaru get to
go on a date with Haruhi?
なぜハルヒが光なんかとデートをしなければならんのだ
Hikaru, where should we go first?
光　最初はどこ行こっか
I forbid any indirect kissing!
I forbid any couple- eating of ice cream!
間接チュー禁止　アイスクリームのカップル食い禁止
Next time, " Operation Haruhi
& Hikaru's First Date"
Ouran High School Host Club will
be waiting for you, next week!
桜蘭高校ホストクラブ　来週も
お待ちしております